http://www.imrmagazine.com/privacy.php

PRIVACY POLICY
1. This privacy policy applies to the Investment Management Review Magazine website www.imrmagazine.com and at Investment Management Review Magazine we take your privacy very seriously. This policy covers the collection, processing and other use of personal data under the Data Protection Act 1998 (“DPA”) and the General Data Protection Regulations (“GDPR”).
2. For the purpose of the DPA and GDPR we are the data controller and any enquiry regarding the collection or processing of your data should be addressed to Sage & Hermes Ltd, 44 Worthington Road, Surbiton, Surrey, KT6 7RX
3. By using the website you consent to this policy.
The information we collect
4. We will collect personal data on this website only if it is directly provided to us by you the user, e.g. your email address, name, home or work address and telephone number and therefore has been provided by you with your consent. Normally you will only provide such details if you wish to sign up for a free newsletter, some other resource / service or are making a purchase from us.
5. We also use analytical and statistical tools that monitor details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data but this data will not identify you personally.
Use of your information
6. We may hold and process personal data that you provide to us in accordance with the DPA and GDPR.
7. The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you and to meet our contractual commitments to you. In addition we may use the information for the following purposes:
7.1. To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service / product changes, that may affect our service;
7.2. If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those that were the subject of a previous sale to you;
7.3. Where you have consented to receive such information, to provide information on other parties products or services that we feel may be of interest to you;
7.4. Where you have consented to receive our newsletter(s), in order that we may provide them to you from time to time.
Disclosure of your information
8. We may disclose your information to regulatory bodies to enable us to comply with the law and to assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.
9. Where you have consented for us to do so, we may provide your data to selected third parties who may contact you about their goods or services that you may be interested in.
10. If you do not want us to use your data for our or third parties’ use, you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us when you email us, or you can do so by writing to us at the address detailed in clause 2, or by sending us an email to privacy@imrmagazine.com at any time.
11. Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.
Controlling the use of your data
12. If you have given us consent to use your data for a particular purpose you can revoke or vary that consent at any time. If you do not want us to use your data or want to vary the consent that you have provided you can write to us at the address detailed in clause 2 or email us at privacy@imrmagazine.com at any time.
Where we store and transfer your data
13. As part of the services offered to you, for example through our website, the information you provide to us may be transferred to and stored in countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) as we use remote website server hosts to provide the website and some aspects of our service, which may be based outside of the EEA, or use servers based outside of the EEA - this is generally the nature of data stored in “the Cloud”.  It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for one of our suppliers, e.g. our website server host, or work for us when temporarily outside of the EEA.
14. A transfer of your personal data may happen if any of our servers are located in a country outside of the EEA or one of our service providers is located in a country outside of the EEA. If we transfer or store your personal data outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected, as outlined in this privacy policy and in accordance with the DPA and GDPR. If you use our service while you are outside the EEA, your personal data may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with these services.
15. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal data, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
16. We may disclose your personal data outside of our group: (a) in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; and (b) if Investment Management Review Magazine is bought by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the assets to transfer to the buyer.  However any such transfer will only be on terms that the confidentiality of your personal data is protected and that the terms of this privacy policy will continue to be complied with by the recipient.
17. Otherwise, we will process, disclose or share your personal data only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or legal process served on us or the website.
18. You have the right to opt out of our processing your personal data for marketing purposes by contacting us at privacy@imrmagazine.com.
Security
19. The transmission of information via the Internet or by email is not completely secure.  Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of data while you are transmitting it to our site and any such transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal data we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
20. Where we have given you, or where you have chosen, a password so that you can access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should choose a password it is not easy for someone to guess.
Third party links
21. You might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies, which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.
Use of cookies
22. Our website uses cookies. We use cookies to gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website. Such information will not identify you personally as it is purely statistical data about our visitors and their use of our website. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. We may also gather information about your general Internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer, as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you. All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.
Learn more about deleting cookies from your devices.
Cookie Name
Domain
Information
_ga
imrmagazine.com
Google Analytics - stores the amount of visits (for each visitor), the time of the first visit, the previous visit, and the current visit
_gid
imrmagazine.com
Google Analytics - used to check approximately how fast people leave: when a visit starts, and approximately ends.
__utmc
imrmagazine.com
Google Analytics - used to check approximately how fast people leave: when a visit starts, and approximately ends (expires quickly).
_gat
imrmagazine.com
Google Analytics - records whether the visitor came from a search engine (and if so, the search keyword used), a link, or from no previous page (e.g. a bookmark).
PHPSESSID
imrmagazine.com
PHP session ID.
LANG
paypal.com
Paypal.
x-csrf-jwt
paypal.com.com
Paypal.
tsrce
paypal.com
Paypal.
ts
paypal.com
Paypal.
nsid
paypal.com
Paypal.
X-PP-SILOVER
paypal.com
Paypal.
AKDC
paypal.com
Paypal.
akavpau_ppsd
paypal.com
Paypal.
_cookiecheck
paypal.com
Paypal.
44907
paypal.com
Paypal.
enforce_policy
paypal.com
Paypal.
x-pp-s
paypal.com
Paypal.
x-csrf-jwt
paypal.com
Paypal.
_gat_PayPal
paypal.com
Paypal.
PYPF
paypalobjects.com
Paypal.
c
stats.paypal.com
Paypal.
session
stats.paypal.com
Paypal.
sc_f
c.paypal.com
Paypal.
test_cookie
doubleclick.net
DoubleClick - serves relevant ads to potential customers and gathers information about how or if you are interacting with these ads.
IDE
doubleclick.net
DoubleClick - used to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.
Your rights
23. The DPA and GDPR give you the right to access information held about you by us. Please write to us or contact us by email if you wish to request confirmation of what personal information we hold relating to you. You can write to us at the address detailed in clause 2 above, or by email to privacy@imrmagazine.com. There is no charge for requesting that we provide you with details of the personal data that we hold. We will provide this information within one month of your requesting the data.
24. You have the right to change the permissions that you have given us in relation to how we may use your date. You also have the right to request that we cease using your data or that we delete all personal data records that we hold relating to you. You can exercise these rights at any time by writing to us at the address detailed in clause 2 above or by email to privacy@imrmagazine.com.
Changes to this policy
25. This policy may be updated periodically so please review the information presented on this page from time to time to be informed of how we use and protect your personal data.
Dated 23rd May 2018
IMR - EDHEC Special Edition 2017
IMR Magazine Winter 2018
Member Login | Join Us | Contact Us | About IMR | Privacy | Home
Member Login | Join Us | Contact UsAbout IMR | Privacy | Home
Copyright ©2018 IMR Magazine Powered by Sage and Hermes
Website design by Vibrance
Copyright ©2018 IMR MagazinePowered by Sage and Hermes
Website design by Vibrance
